[{"answer": "Who was the father", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What man had access to her", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Father my friend, but I don't see him as a candidate", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Obviously there was", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "From their heads..", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No, they say it came from the waste paper basket", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Is that where they say it came from... ", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Where'd it come from before that", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " God loves you", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No... do you", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "So, someone else could have done it", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "And in your eyes", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I remember when you    was a little girl my friend. You come back    from the movies and you'd say", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Who are you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Shortly after she came to us", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I was appalled, just as you are now", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "My dear, I don't think a communion wafer has the recommended daily allowance of anything", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Yes, of God", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " Numbers... you can spend your whole life counting and never reach the end", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I hope not. It's a terrible thing to be dropped on your head", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I could never be a mother", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "If you did want one, how'd you go about getting one", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "What is it", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What sheets", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "We're not in the Middle Ages, Sister", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It made them uncomfortable. And i", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Your mother was a resident of Saint Catherines home before you moved her", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And you had a sister who died in the convent", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "No I'm not", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " Yes I am", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "I really love you", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "As much as God loves you", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "She drank too much. That's what killed her", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I don't think I care to know", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Because I am a moral person", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Bullshit yourself", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "that place doesn't have a corner on morality..", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "You just said..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I wasn't. I wasn't. She was the pretty one. She died, why not me? I never said my morning prayers. And I was ugly, I was scrawny, I had buck teeth and freckles all over my face, do you know what the nun called me, Sister my friend, called me my friend", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, because I... yeah, yeah I left the Church cause I had freckles", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Because I was afraid", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Because I wasn't worthy", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Agnes-of-God.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I feel as if I've eaten glass", "qsentId": 46}]